<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>论文 on mannuan</title>
    <link>https://mannuan.github.io/categories/%E8%AE%BA%E6%96%87/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 论文 on mannuan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 11:02:01 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mannuan.github.io/categories/%E8%AE%BA%E6%96%87/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CASCADE: Contextual Sarcasm Detection in Online Discussion Forums翻译和解读</title>
      <link>https://mannuan.github.io/post/20190717110201/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 11:02:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mannuan.github.io/post/20190717110201/</guid>
      <description>摘要  The literature in automated sarcasm detection has mainly focused on lexical-, syntactic- and semantic-level analysis of text. However, a sarcastic sentence can be expressed with contextual presumptions, background and commonsense knowledge. In this paper, we propose a ContextuAl SarCasm DEtector (CASCADE), which adopts a hybrid approach of both content- and context-driven modeling for sarcasm detection in online social media discussions. For the latter, CASCADE aims at extracting contextual information from the discourse of a discussion thread.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latex常用设置</title>
      <link>https://mannuan.github.io/post/20190709170202/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 17:02:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mannuan.github.io/post/20190709170202/</guid>
      <description>bib文件点击跳转 在.tex文件开头加上\usepackage[backref]{hyperref}。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Representing Social Media Users for Sarcasm Detection论文翻译和解读</title>
      <link>https://mannuan.github.io/post/20190704162010/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 16:20:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mannuan.github.io/post/20190704162010/</guid>
      <description>Representing Social Media Users for Sarcasm Detection  用于讽刺检测的社交媒体用户的特征表示
 摘要 在上下文讽刺检测的背景下，两种表示作者特征的方式：
 使用贝叶斯的方式直接表示作者的讽刺倾向；
 密集向量嵌入可以学习到作者和文本之间的交互；
 使用reddit评论的SARC数据集，双向的rnn可以提高性能；
  贝叶斯的方法在同质的上下文中是足够的，密集的向量嵌入是有价值的 the Bayesian approach suffices in homogeneous contexts, whereas the added power of the dense embeddings proves valuable in more diverse ones. 
  介绍  Irony and sarcasm1 are extreme examples of context-dependence in language. Given only the text Great idea! or What a hardship!, we cannot resolve the speaker’s intentions unless we have in- sight into the circumstances of utterance – who is speaking, and to whom, and how the content relates to the preceding discourse (Clark, 1996).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>